

ABOUT ME

I am interested in everything related to IT, especially in Web Programming. I'd love to get more experience on this field since I like investigation, training and adquiring knowledge. I'd like to develope myself in this profession.

For this reason, I am searching a Company willing to offer me a job among its developers. As an exchange, I offer you my compromise and dedication, and I expect these qualities would be pleasant and friendly for your team work.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cell phone: +54 9 1169764992

Email: jonathan.moya93@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-

emanuel-moya/?locale=en_US

EDUCATION

UTN University

Mechanical Engineering 2017-2019

Information Systems Engineering 2019-Present.

CoderHouse

front-end developer 2021-Present.

JONATHAN EMANUEL MOYA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Duty manager

Video Club La Terminal From 2012-02 To 2012-09

- Customer Support.
- · Product organizer.
- Logistics and data computation.

Cashier/Stocker

Bazar Varieties From 2013-02 To 2014-01

- Collection work at the cash register, including transactions in cash and with cards.
- Change of prices and labeling of products of shelves.
- Attention and advice to clients, guaranteeing that find the product tidy and visible.

Data Entry

Fresenius Medical Care From 2015-03 To 2018-05

- Preparation and presentation of reports.
- Management and documentation of relevant information in the computer system.

Freelancer

Web Developer Freelancer 2020-Present

- Website development with CSS, HTML and JavaScript.
- Website maintenance and optimization user interfaces.

SKILLS

- Clear and precise communication.
- Adaptable to changes.
- Teamwork.
- Responsible.
- Problem resolution.
- · Creative.